Get your sunglasses ready because today is going to be a really colorful and bright video with these
three over-the-knee heels from Up2Step and I'm going to combine them with catsuits today and
create some different looks for each over-the-knee boot and looking forward to it because I think
they're really awesome so let's start with the first outfit first he'll net
for later
I chose a black and white catsuit because I wanted to make the red pop and I think it
was a success. What do you think?
It's a nice contrast and the catsuit is also
matte so we have that theme in both the catsuits and the boots
and for sure the boots
are the eye catcher here. I know it's a question of faith
if you like platform boots and platform heels
or not. I love them because they're so much more comfortable than
boots without platforms and I also love the look of them but I have some without platforms for later
but first I still want to admire these because I think they're really cool. I've been asked a lot
about how to style over knee boots and to be honest my preferred options are catsuits because
then you have one smooth outfit and do not have to take care of different layers or hemlines or
whatever but can focus on the boots. By the way do you remember this catsuit from one of my first
jumpsuit up videos? I still have it and I'm so happy that I could use it again here. I just
recently took some pictures with it but I think it's a really great fit especially with the red
heels and it's really colorful together with my hair so I think I'll do the outfit with the blue
next. Blue heels to be honest I chose them because I finally wanted to have
some boots matching my hair. So here we go my very first pair of blue over knee
boots and they're really sparkly that's what I like about them so it's nice to
let them catch the light and also they're pointed not my favorite kind of
shoe form but I think it looks really edgy and cool in this case and also
together with the silver catsuit I chose it's a really spacey outfit a bit I felt
that combining the dark heels with a black catsuit would have been a bit too
gloomy so here we go with the silver I think it works really well together
it's super new so it's still really slippery on the floor but pretty comfy
actually even for pointed heels so I think they look really fancy I immediately
feel more elegant with them and they're also soft so even though they look like
they have these little chips of color on them it doesn't feel rough for reasons
and kind of like suede leather so I love them from the design aspect I love that
we have a plateau even with the pointed shoes so there is a point of plateau so
to say I think that is really something you see not every day and I'm going to
switch over to the next pair of boots now also pointed but without plateau
holographic lilac purple pink last outfit and this time I opted for a black
catsuit indeed because I think again as with the first outfit the catsuit
dark catsuit makes the heels pop out so much more with this holographic I don't
know purple lilac pink color so this time we have pointed heels without a
plateau and I have to say I find without plateau more uncomfortable just my five
cents the fabric is PVC fabric this time it's quite firm and thick so I think
best option is to stand here because bending the knee isn't that easy because
of the non stretchy fabric but it looks really good I have to give that if you
want to stand out of the crowd then these boots are for you it's quite funny
because the PVC of the heels is sticking to the catsuit which is also PVC so it
makes funny noises. Of course I can close it as well. I also want to point out that they have a metal heel so it's not in a
color of the boot but silver and I think I could add some silver accessories to
pull it even more together but I just wanted to put the focus on the boots
this time. As for rating my favorite pair was I think blue over knee boots with
the silver catsuit followed by the red boots with the black and white catsuit
and then this outfit yeah I think that's my rating. Tell me yours in the comments
and leave a thumb up, subscribe to my channel thanks to up to step for
gifting me these boots. I really love them and I hope you all enjoyed this video. I will see you
in the next one. Have a nice day. Bye!